- Juliana. Take this.
- What is it?
A way out.
- (gunshot)
- (gasps)
- What is this?
- It's newsreel film.
- The Man in the High Castle.
- It shows us winning the war.
- Yeah, but we didn't win the war.
- Once the Fuhrer dies,
there will be war.
- (man speaks German)
- TAGOMI: This is our moment.
We must not hesitate
to seize it.
They're building an atomic bomb.
JULIANA: You take me
to the Man in the High Castle.
Ask him if he wants to see me.
- You're him, aren't you?
- I'm Abendsen.
Hawthorne Abendsen.
Every film where
the Japs won the war,
sooner or later San Francisco
is wiped out by an A-bomb,
every one except this one,
where this bastard dies
as a Nazi
- in an alley somewhere.
- His name is George Dixon.
What's he got to do with Trudy?
He's her father.
JULIANA: I need a diplomatic visa
to get out of
the Pacific States.
TAGOMI: But if by trying,
you compound tragedy...
My name is Juliana Crain.
I work with Joe Blake.
I need asylum.
SMITH: I have orders for you,
from Berlin,
from Reichsminister Heusmann.
JOE: And what makes
either of you think
- I want to see him?
- He's your father.
Your father is one of the most
powerful men in the Reich.
He could get you
anything you want.
Anything he wants to give me,
I don't want it.
HEUSMANN: Have you heard of Lebensborn?
Racially desirable women
volunteer to have the babies
at the Lebensborn
birthing houses,
to be raised in line
with the party ideals.
This was your birthing house, Josef.
(Himmler speaks German)
I'm your godfather.
I look forward to seeing
a great deal more of you.
ADLER: Your son has
a serious disease.
You know what must be done.
- Give me more time.
- Withholding his diagnosis
is a crime against the state.
If you won't take care
of this today,
I'll have to do it tomorrow.
(muffled yelling)
JOHN: What happened is
just a terrible tragedy, Alice.
What if it's more than that?
GARY: You flip the switch,
and you get the hell out of there.
FRANK: How long have I got?
Plenty, as long as you head
straight for the exit.
(men yelling)
♪ ♪
TAGOMI: I went to the park
to meditate.
It brought me to a strange place.
It was San Francisco,
but not this San Francisco.
You are different
than what I remember.
You are free.
Why do you want this?
TAGOMI: Proof that something like this
should never happen again.
KIDO: Our empire does not
possess such a device.
The film is real.
TAGOMI: With your help,
it is my intention
to show this film.
SMITH: What you're seeing, gentlemen,
is a hydrogen bomb,
with a magnitude
a thousand times more powerful
- than anything in our arsenal.
- HEUSMANN: I know the casualties
will be higher,
but that may be necessary.
You can't build a better world
if there's nothing left of it!
- What the hell's going on?
- Your father's a traitor, Joe.
(speaking German in unison)
(Nazis continue in German)
But I won't tell them
about what you or Father said.
Be proud of me.
Tell Father to be proud.
(sobbing): Thomas, please don't go.
(distorted, echoing scream)
You knew what would happen.
You showed me the film,
- and you knew.
- No, the only thing
I knew was that you,
Juliana Crain,
were the only hope
any of us had.
You were in the films,
over and over again.
Some of the people you knew,
we started seeing them, too,
revolving around you,
like an atom...
They would change,
different behavior,
different relationships,
different points of view.
I knew that was the key.
The goodness in you, Juliana.
That's what I put my money on.
Hey, sis.
What if you haven't seen
this film?
(birds chirping)
(crow cawing in distance)
(engine idling)
- (gunfire stops)
- (birds screeching in distance)
♪ ♪
(film projector whirring, clicking)
♪ Edelweiss ♪
♪ Every morning ♪
♪ You greet ♪
♪ Me ♪
♪ Small and white ♪
♪ Clean and bright ♪
♪ You look happy ♪
♪ To meet ♪
♪ Me ♪
♪ Blossom of snow ♪
♪ May you bloom ♪
♪ And grow ♪
♪ Bloom and grow ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ Edelweiss ♪
♪ Bless my homeland ♪
♪ Forever. ♪
(birds chirping)
(footsteps approaching)
(door creaks open)
(metallic squeak,
hose shuts off)
(panting)
(German song playing)
(electricity crackling, prisoner screaming)
Josef.
- (song continues playing)
- (heart beating loudly)
(prisoner screaming)
Only then can you face the truth.
(German song continues)
(prisoner's echoing scream)
(screams)
(wind whistling)
(siren wailing)
(man counting down in Japanese over speakers)
(countdown continues over speakers)
(countdown ends)
(deep rumbling)
(objects vibrating)
(rumbling continues)
♪ ♪
(siren continues wailing)
Kanpai.
OTHERS: Kanpai!
(low chatter)
(door closes)
KIDO: How long before the Nazis
know they have been deceived?
They will analyze the data
from this test,
compare it to the bomb n the films...
A thousand times more powerful.
Then they will realize
they should have attacked us
when they had the chance.
Perhaps they still will.
By other means.
(upbeat country music playing)
(indistinct chatter)
(horn honking)
JULIANA: Hey, Clyde.
Anything?
As a matter of fact...
Couple of days ago.
- Who's Aunt Judy?
- You read my mail?
It's a postcard.
- Listen, I need to send a reply.
- Okay.
Here, on the house.
Perfect. Thank you.
There's no return address.
You don't know the address?
No, they just moved there.
All right.
You looking to find somebody,
find something in the Zone,
you want to take a stroll
down to the Grand Palace.
♪ ♪
Head for the saloon entrance
down them stairs.
Blow past
them fancy double doors,
breeze past the piano
to the bar,
like you know
where you're going.
Don't be shy.
There's a semi-private room
on the right.
And the guy there might be
able to help you out,
name's Wyatt Price.
Wyatt Price?
I, um, I-I need
a mailing address
for someone in Santa Fe.
Name's Judy Bridger.
Bridger with a "D."
(chuckles)
Come back tomorrow.
(wind chimes tinkling)
♪ ♪
(sighs) Happens to every
traveler, sooner or later.
Antsy to get home,
back to their own world.
It's been what? Five months?
Six, more like.
I'd say it was way past
antsy today.
Something's wrong.
Yeah.
(car horns honking, indistinct shouting)
Welcome home, sir.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
(car engine starts)
(elevator bell chimes)
Hello, my girls.
- Daddy.
- You're back.
I missed you two.
- Where's your mother?
- AMY: Out.
Oh?
What about Bridget?
JENNIFER: Mama sent her home.
All right.
Let's see what the three of us
can rustle up for supper,
shall we?
(wind chimes tinkling in distance)
Tru.
Hey.
Gosh, you're burning up.
Ma?
It's Juliana.
No. Juliana's dead.
No, baby. I'm right here.
Right here.
Sorry.
I forget.
Me, too.
(exhales)
(chuckles)
Remember when you were six
and you got the measles?
I never had the measles, Jules.
My Trudy did.
I stayed with her all night
long, stroking her hair.
I thought my arm would fall off.
The moon was shining in
the window.
I laid down next to her.
Stayed with her
till she fell asleep.
(gunshot)
(sighs) Poor dear was pacing
all morning like a convict
- in the yard.
- Yep.
I've urged her to go back to her
world for months, now,
and she's tried,
but she seems... stuck.
I don't know
what's stopping her.
(scoffs) You are, dear. You are.
You died in her world,
and she died in ours.
Yet here you are together.
(sighs) And look what you've
become to one another.
A pair of matched magnets,
both drawn together.
- (chuckles) Sisters.
- Mm-hmm.
- All right.
- (Juliana laughs)
AMY: Do you like Berlin?
- Did you see the Fuhrer?
- (opera music playing)
He gave me my medal.
- That's so cool.
- SMITH: Mmm.
No bragging about it at school,
young lady.
I promise.
You keep that promise and
I might let you try it on.
- Really?
- Mmm.
- What about me?
- (elevator bell chimes)
Yeah, okay. You, too.
(heels clacking on floor nearby)
(opera music continues)
How was your trip?
SMITH: It's good to be back.
I took the train out
to our old house today.
The lawn needs mowing.
Why would you do that?
There's a little girl living
there now, in Thomas's room.
She waved to me.
Helen...
How did you get back?
Nice people who live there now,
they gave me a ride.
(door opens)
Mmm.
(singing indistinctly)
(grunts, groans)
Josef,
how good it is to see
your face again.
It brings me so much...
joy.
H-How are they treating you?
JOE: How are they tr-treating you?
Very well, very well.
They-they-they are,
they are teaching me, Josef.
They are teaching me.
What are they teaching you?
That-that I was wrong.
To go against the-the Fuhrer
and-and the Party.
D-Do you understand, Josef?
The Party is right.
Do not resist.
Promise me, Josef.
Promise me, please.
Your life depends on it.
(security door buzzes in distance)
I pr-I promise.
HEUSMANN: Good. Good, good.
Tell them how it was, my son,
how we shared a...
a bond of blood,
our name.
A bond of love.
Our name! Our blood!
Our name!
Our blood!
Our name! Our blood!
JOE: "Martin Heusmann was my father.
"His false beliefs came to infect me.
"We were both guilty
"of wrong thinking against the Fuhrer,
"which gave rise to
an unspeakable criminal scheme
"to assassinate our great leader,
"our one true... father.
"Wrong thinking against the Fuhrer,
"against the Party,
- (grunts)
- "against the true science
"of national socialism.
"Martin Heusmann...
(groans)
was my father."
JOE (whispering): Father?
HEUSMANN: Save yourself, my son.
A heart of steel.
(repeating same German phrase)
♪ ♪
(John Philip Sousa march playing)
YOUNG ABENDSEN: The
plucky Brits have the Hun
on the run in Africa.
ABENDSEN: I did the headlines.
Cut up newspapers
like ransom notes.
YOUNG ABENDSEN: As England
holds off Hitler, American
and British bombers deliver
crushing raids on Germany.
- So the first film was a fake.
- Please.
A fiction, a message in
a bottle to open people's minds.
- What if the Allies won the war?
- Exactly.
What if?
YOUNG ABENDSEN: No matter
what the Luftwaffe
sends at our brave airmen, they
fend off attack after attack.
JULIANA: Where'd you get the footage?
ABENDSEN: I was working
in Canon City after the war, '48,
crummy little movie theater.
Hawthorne was the projectionist.
ABENDSEN: I squirreled away
all kinds of celluloid scraps...
Old docs, newsreels... so,
I cobbled something together,
and we showed it a few times.
- Oh, people went nuts.
- Mm.
- They were cheering and screaming.
- Mm-hmm.
Kissing strangers.
We didn't mean to kick over
the hornets' nest, but we did.
YOUNG ABENDSEN: Jubilation follows
as America celebrates victory
in Europe.
CAROLINE: Word got around
that Hawthorne was some sort
of prophet
of the Resistance,
which he wasn't.
- No.
- Not at first.
That's because the real films
started coming to our door.
YOUNG ABENDSEN: On the
other side of the planet,
our courageous Marines
take island after island.
CAROLINE: Travelers like Trudy
would bring them
from their worlds,
- and then, the Resistance
would get them to us. -Mm-hmm.
YOUNG ABENDSEN: It's clear this
boat will not go down quietly.
America is forced to unleash
its secret weapon.
Victory in Japan is celebrated
as grateful crowds give cheer.
Evil is defeated, and freedom
is restored once and for all.
(music ends)
- (Caroline laughs)
- So...
Can you rewind?
- Just-just near the end.
- Yeah.
- The people celebrating
in the streets. -Mm-hmm.
(projector clicks)
(clicking)
JULIANA: There.
That's me...
That... that little girl.
When were you gonna
tell me that?
I didn't know that was you,
I swear.
Are you sure that's you?
Yes. I was seven years old.
It was February of 1942,
the day after
the U.S. retook Hawaii.
The whole city was
in the streets.
Oh, I remember that.
We were all so happy.
- We thought the tide had turned.
- It's coincidence.
- It's serendipity.
- It's more than that, Hawthorne.
It has to be.
This proves it.
Proves what?
What is that look?
Huh?
It proves
that my time is up, Juliana.
It's time for somebody else
to take the reins.
How can somebody else
take the reins?
Why do you think
I burned the films?
Time is running out!
Bad guys are closing in,
and I'm tired, Juliana.
It's time for somebody else.
- No. No. No!
- (Abendsen sighs)
You can either embrace
your destiny or dodge it.
Maybe I'm tired
of your idea of my destiny!
My idea? You turned up
in my little movie.
- What are the odds?
- The odds? You made that happen!
- Wasn't me.
- Wasn't you.
You know, the first time we met,
you told me
I didn't want to know
how the film of my life ends.
But Hawthorne, I want to know!
How does it fucking end?
That depends on you, chickie.
(sighs)
He didn't burn all of 'em.
(wind chimes tinkling)
(distant wooden rattling)
(insects chirping)
(wooden rattling)
(furniture scrapes on floor)
(loon calling)
(Juliana sighs)
(stairs creaking quietly)
(gun chamber clicks)
(panting softly)
(soft thud)
(gasps)
(muffled yell)
(muffled grunting)
CAROLINE: Oh! Oh!
(Abendsen grunts)
(rattling)
(Caroline yelps, Abendsen groans)
(door creaks open)
(Caroline and Abendsen gasp)
- (Caroline screams)
- Are you okay?
- ABENDSEN: Fine.
- (gunshot)
- (clattering)
- (muffled groaning)
(clanking on ground)
(panting)
(sighs)
- (sighs) Thank God...
- I'm still here?
(muffled groaning)
- Here now. Here. Here.
- Oh.
Here, here. We got it.
There, there.
- (Caroline sighs)
- ABENDSEN: Yeah.
TRUDY: Who are they?
CAROLINE: Bounty hunters?
No.
The Reich, maybe.
We got to go. Now.
ABENDSEN: All right, this is it.
Get out.
What? Why are we stopping?
Hawthorne, we're coming with you.
CAROLINE: Get out. Come on.
It's safer if we split up.
- JULIANA: What about you?
- We'll be all right.
Now you all just get a room
at Danny's
- and lay low until things cool off.
- Yeah.
Here's some cash
to tide you over.
I'll get in touch
when it's safe,
send someone for you.
By the way, your friend,
the trade minister?
He's who I sent the films to,
the ones I didn't burn.
But he's Japanese.
We need friends
on the other side now.
Allies. He's important,
influential.
You and he have
a deep connection.
What are you talking about?
Huh?
What do you mean by that?
You want to know...
how it ends for you?
(engine starts)
Tagomi knows.
You're in every damn one
of those films.
Get Tagomi to show them to you.
♪ ♪
(man speaking Japanese)
- (grunts softly)
- (man speaking Japanese over P.A.)
(speaking Japanese)
- (grunting)
- (people speaking Japanese)
(man yelling)
(people crying, whimpering)
(yelling)
(men speaking Japanese)
(shouting in Japanese)
(distant shouting)
- (phone ringing in distance)
- (distant whimpering, shouting)
(machine gun fire)
- (distant shouting)
- (machine gun fire)
(shouting)
(phone ringing in distance)
KIDO: They told me
not to waste my time
looking at your application.
Because I'm "hapa."
Hapa?
Hawaiian slang for...
kon-kétsuji.
So, American born
and half-white.
(chuckles)
(repeats Japanese phrase)
Where would your true loyalty
lie, Sergeant Nakamura-hapa?
With your Japanese father,
or with your mother's people,
who bombed this building
and killed the brave man
you hope to replace?
I only ask for an opportunity
to prove myself.
(machine gun fire)
KIDO: This morning,
the reprisals have prompted
a civic-minded citizen
to offer
what may be a solid tip...
on one of the last rebel leaders
still at large.
(machine gun fire)
And Sergeant?
Yes, sir.
I cannot interrogate a corpse.
(horns honking)
(footsteps approaching)
SMITH: Joe.
Oberstgruppenfuhrer.
SMITH: So,
Reichsfuhrer Himmler
is sending you
to our embassy in San Francisco,
and I'm to provide
a plausible cover.
"Deputy Trade Attaché."
We'll furnish a clean passport
and the necessary credentials.
SMITH: Give us a couple of days
to get it all in order.
- Thank you, sir.
- The Reichsfuhrer's
got your future
all mapped out for you, Joe.
But I'll bet he didn't think
- about the present.
- Sir?
Some walking-around money.
Manhattan these days,
almost as expensive as Berlin.
Thank you, sir.
I'll pay you back.
I'm sorry about your father, Joe.
I'm sorry, too, sir.
About your son.
(elevator bell dings)
I want you to take care
of this personally, Erich.
Discreetly.
Yes, sir.
(footsteps receding)
TURNER: They can't pull
this shit on me last minute.
The Fritz Kuhn deal is my deal.
I don't need some German chick
fresh off the rocket plane
to tell me which way's up.
Nicole Dormer.
German chick.
Sorry.
Billy Turner.
Minister of Propaganda,
and world-class idiot.
Welcome to New York, Fraulein.
- First time?
- Hardly.
- Miss Dormer...
- Nicole.
Nicole. I think there are some
transatlantic crossed wires
on this little
renaming ceremony.
"Fascism is freedom"?
"Freedom to prosper."
"Freedom to explore."
"Freedom from fear."
"Freedom to propagate"?
- That's the new campaign.
- New?
Sounds rather familiar.
Brand-new.
"Procreate to Populate,
with Pride"?
That's the spring rollout to
inspire our young brides to...
Fuck and be fertile?
I wouldn't quite put it that way.
This image is perfect for
a message from the Reich.
Warmer, more maternal.
Something like...
Forgive my English...
Perhaps... "Now more than ever,
we care about you."
That's not bad.
But let's not get ahead
of ourselves, schatzi.
Agreed. Let's not.
I have thoughts of how to film it.
Yeah, well,
what I was starting to say,
we're-we're doing that in-house.
Got our top people on it.
(laughs)
Silly me. I forgot.
My uncle desires a fresh face
for the new propaganda effort
in America.
Reichsminister Goebbels
is your uncle?
In a manner of speaking.
I see.
Wunderbar.
So happy you see.
Because we don't have
much time to prepare.
I'll need three cameras,
a crew and a crane.
Danke, schatzi.
See you at the premiere.
(crowd chatter, fireworks, rock music in distance)
(sighs)
Tru. There's something
I should have said...
months ago.
Then say it.
No time like the present.
In this world...
in my world...
your father dedicated his life
to the Resistance.
(quietly): And I had to kill him.
To stop something terrible
from happening.
Hawthorne told me.
The "Dixon" you killed
wasn't my dad.
The Nazis killed my dad in my world.
(sighs)
Hey. You have nothing
to feel bad about.
- Come on.
- (laughs)
Thank you.
You know what?
(both laugh)
What?
I'd kill...
(exhales)
for a little music
and a tall, cold one.
Uh, uh, no.
- No, we c...
- (people whooping)
(whispers):
We can't go out there.
(jazzy, upbeat intro plays)
♪ ♪
♪ Forget your troubles,
come on, get happy ♪
♪ You better chase
your blues away ♪
♪ Shout hallelujah ♪
♪ Come on, get happy ♪
♪ Get ready
for the judgment day... ♪
Is there anything else
I can get you señoritas?
Uh, I'll have another shot
of I.W. Harper over ice.
Tru?
- I'm... fine.
- Muy bien.
Thank you.
(man whoops)
♪ We're going
to the promised land ♪
♪ We're gonna cross the river ♪
♪ Wash your sins in the tide ♪
- ♪ It's all so peaceful ♪
- Hey.
♪ On the other side... ♪
Well, hello there, Santa Fe.
Well, hello.
♪ You better chase
your blues away... ♪
That was fast.
What do I owe you?
You can buy me a drink.
Done.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
And, uh, who's this?
This is my sister.
Wyatt Price.
Nice to meet you, Wyatt.
Likewise, sister.
So how long do you think
it'll take to get there?
Wing and a Prayer Postal?
Sure I could drive you both
to Santa Fe faster.
- (laughing): It's 400 miles.
- We could leave tonight.
I thought the roads were full
of bandits and highwaymen.
Oh, they are.
It'd be an adventure.
(all chuckle)
Right. I think I'll, um,
- just drop this in the mail.
- (laughs)
Well, if you won't drive with me
to Santa Fe
by the light
of the silvery moon,
how about a dance, sister?
No, uh, thank you.
- I think I'm turning in.
- (clears throat)
What about you, Santa Fe?
Would you like
to have a dance with me?
- TRUDY: Go ahead.
- (applause)
- Go for it.
- SINGER: This song was written
by a few of my friends out west.
This is the first time
we've ever played it before.
♪ ♪
I'll take a chance.
I have something to confess.
You don't know how to dance.
Indeed, I can't.
Right. Neither can I.
Blind leading the blind.
♪ Fools ♪
♪ Rush in... ♪
WYATT: And I have something else
to confess.
What's that?
I still don't know your name.
No, you don't.
♪ I can't help... ♪
♪ ♪
(fireworks exploding
in distance)
(indistinct shouting nearby)
(gunshots)
(indistinct shouting
and laughter)
- (exhales)
- (indistinct conversation)
(sighs)
Like this every night?
Except Sundays and holidays,
yeah.
- Right. -You spent much time
in the Zone?
- Mm-mm.
- Hmm.
Not much.
Mmm...
It's exciting.
It feels dangerous and free.
It's both.
There's barely any
law and order.
Everyone here has got
some kind of hustle...
just to get by.
The Zone is a mess.
But it's our mess.
(fireworks exploding
in distance)
(chuckles) God, I can't imagine
what it would be like
to grow up free
in a place like this.
Well, I didn't grow up here.
Came over with my folks,
to New York, then here.
- Refugee, two times.
- Hence the accent.
Oh, keen ear.
(laughs)
Well, thanks very much.
(whooping in distance)
So what's your hustle, Wyatt?
Hmm. Black market mostly.
- That guy you were talking to.
- Business associate.
- You buying or selling?
- Wee bit of both.
Mmm. Guns?
No offense.
But I don't know you
well enough.
Fair enough.
And what's your hustle?
What really brings you to town?
Sorry, but I...
I don't know you well enough.
(clears throat)
(sighs)
Will I see you tomorrow?
Yeah, I'd like that.
(clears throat)
Well, you know where to find me.
Juliana.
(quietly):
(keys jangle, lock clicks)
(door opens)
JULIANA:
Trudy?
(door closes)
- Hey, Tru?
- (water splashing)
(gurgling)
No, no, no. Shh. Okay.
- Okay.
- (gasps)
- Breathe.
We will see each other again.
(both panting)
Okay, we have to go, okay?
We can't stay here.
How? It's too dangerous.
Trust me.
(wind chimes tinkling)
♪ ♪
(knocking at door)
Were you ever going to call me?
I'm so sorry, Joe.
Are you coming to the ceremony?
Wasn't invited.
I'm filming it.
I'm making a documentary.
So that's what you're doing now?
The next Leni Riefenstahl.
Why not?
She turned 60 last summer.
Time she retired.
What are you doing here?
I just told you.
No.
What are you doing... here?
I wanted to see you, of course.
And I want to film you.
All right, you want to film me.
Why?
Because you're one of us.
I want to make a film
about us Lebensborn.
We have a special destiny
in the history of the Reich.
And its future.
Yes.
Yes, we do.
(quietly):
My God.
What did they do to you?
It's okay.
I'm here now.
It's me.
(Joe exhales)
(exhales)
It's okay.
You're okay.
(panting)
(bedsprings creak)
Will that be all, ma'am?
Uh, if-if you'll just lay out
my choices for tomorrow.
Yes, ma'am.
I saw Joe Blake the other day.
He's back in New York?
Mm. Well, just passing through.
He's on his way
to San Francisco.
Is he coming tomorrow?
No, I don't think so, honey.
Listen...
(sighs)
I wanted to talk about tomorrow.
Now,
tomorrow,
as a family,
we are gonna be celebrating
your brother.
We want the world to know
how proud we are of Thomas,
don't we?
And the choice that he made.
No matter how we feel.
How do you feel, Daddy?
Oh, honey.
(sighs)
I wake up in the morning
and, um...
I remember he's not here.
(sighs softly)
And then I have
to remind myself that,
because of what he did,
the message that he sent,
he's not ours anymore.
He's not just our Thomas.
He kind of belongs
to everyone now, you know?
So it's okay to be happy
and sad tomorrow?
Yes, of course.
Of course.
You just try to be brave,
try to...
do the best you can,
like Thomas would.
All right?
♪ ♪
We'll get through this, Helen.
We have to.
♪ ♪
(military drumming)
Higher.
Schnell.
(drumming continues)
(shutters clicking)
(drumming stops)
John.
Today is a day of remembrance
and a day for celebration.
It is indeed, Reichsmarschall.
- REPORTER: Mr. Smith, this way!
- REPORTER 2: Over here, sir,
- please! -Mr. Smith! -Mr. Smith,
can you look this way, please?
REPORTER 3: Mr. Rockwell,
look at the camera!
- REPORTER 4: Mr. Smith.
- REPORTER 5: John Smith!
- One picture, please!
- REPORTER 6: Mr. Smith.
Edgar, so glad you could make it.
How could I have missed
such an occasion, Helen?
Your son is an inspiration to
the youth of the entire Reich,
- a hero to last a thousand years.
- Mm.
May I?
(muffled chatter)
WOMAN (muffled): Mrs. Smith?
Mrs. Smith?
Mrs. Smith, please,
any special words for our readers
on this very special day?
It would be appreciated.
It would mean so much.
I... Mrs. Smith.
Thelma.
Who is that?
Nicole Dormer.
Daughter of Ernst Dormer.
As in Dormer Pharmaceuticals?
I've tried Dormer's sedatives,
but I had no idea he made
such world-class stimulants.
Introduce me, Edgar.
Perhaps later.
You behave.
(chuckles softly)
(urinating)
I'm told to expect a call
from Berlin this evening.
Scheisse.
What's his mood?
Apoplectic.
He's particularly upset
about losing
three of his precious Lebensborn.
I told you
we should've sent more men.
Well, we had to go lean
and mean, George,
keep Smith from sniffing this out.
Pin the failure of the raid
on a traitor in Smith's office.
You must have shit
on all of 'em.
Which I'm saving
for a rainy day.
Edgar,
it's about to fucking pour.
Look,
whether this shite sticks
to the bottom of his boot
or to yours,
Smith has other vulnerabilities.
Mrs. Smith,
who, at 10:00 this morning,
at this solemn occasion
honoring her son
and in the presence
of the Reichsmarschall
of North America,
smells
like a goddamn distillery.
- (water running)
- BOY: ♪ The sun on the meadow ♪
♪ Is summery warm ♪
♪ The stag in the forest ♪
♪ Runs free ♪
♪ But gathered together ♪
♪ To greet the storm ♪
♪ Tomorrow ♪
♪ Belongs to me ♪
♪ The babe in his cradle is... ♪
- (quietly): Thelma.
- Hmm?
You spectacular, mystical siren.
I just might have a juicy tidbit
for your column coming soon.
My stock in trade;
I love juicy.
♪ Says a whisper ♪
♪ Arise, arise ♪
I know you do.
♪ Tomorrow belongs ♪
♪ To me ♪
♪ To me. ♪
Dear friends and neighbors,
we are most privileged
to have with us
the Reichsmarschall
of North America,
George Lincoln Rockwell.
We gather here today
to honor...
a true hero of the Reich.
When the hour of decision came
for Thomas Smith,
he rose to the occasion
in a way that admirably
reflected upon his father.
Without wavering,
without self-pity...
- Zoom in.
- Thomas Smith, on his own,
made the ultimate sacrifice
for a community, a country,
a cause.
Surely, Thomas Smith
shall forever stand
a peerless exemplar...
of Aryan youth.
And as we remember this day,
let us absorb a great lesson:
In the hour of decision,
in the hour of crisis,
when we look for leadership,
and for courage,
to whom do we look?
Pan to the Smith family.
Are you nuts? I'll be shot.
If you don't,
I'll have you shot.
ROCKWELL: Covered in medals.
(audience chuckles)
But sometimes,
we are better served
when we look to... a boy.
A boy...
with a dream in his heart.
Sieg Heil!
AUDIENCE: Sieg Heil! Sieg Heil!
Sieg Heil! Sieg Heil!
Sieg Heil!
(rain falling)
(thunder rumbles)
(film projector whirring)
(projector continues whirring)
♪ ♪
(thunder rumbles)
(knocking at door)
(wind chimes tinkling)
(thunder rumbling)
You just missed him.
He took the back stairs.
(door opens)
Joe.
Raeder.
What are you doing here?
I brought your new passport
and credentials, as arranged.
(clears throat)
Yeah, right.
Sorry.
All right.
"Junior Trade Attaché
"Joseph...
- Cinadella."
- "Chin-adella."
Chinadella.
Right. Thanks.
You have everything you need?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
This time last year, this was...
was my, my world.
Can you believe it was
all so... so simple?
Those pallets, th-those planks,
those bricks...
this shovel.
(Raeder grunts)
(woman singing in foreign language)